If we scroll through our DataFrame a bit more,
إذا انتقلنا من خلال DataFrame أكثر قليلاً،
we'll notice that Pandas automatically collapses some columns
فسوف نلاحظ أن Pandas تطوي بشكل تلقائي بعض الأعمدة
and rows of larger DataSets like this one, which you can see here.
والصفوف من DataSets أكبر مثل هذه، والتي يمكنك رؤيتها هنا.
Between row 29 and row 18,971,
بين الصف 29 والصف 18,971،
all of the rows are collapsed using these ellipses here.
يتم طي جميع الصفوف باستخدام علامات الحذف هذه هنا.
And the same thing is true if we scroll right here and check out all of our columns.
ونفس الشيء صحيح إذا انتقلنا إلى هنا وراجعنا كل الأعمدة.
Every column between duration and salary was again collapsed using these ellipses.
تم طي كل عمود بين المدة والراتب مرة أخرى باستخدام علامة الحذف هذه.
Pandas does this because viewing large DataSets takes up too much space.
يقوم Pandas بذلك لأن عرض DataSets كبيرة يشغل مساحة كبيرة جدًا.
And scrolling that much can cause headaches.
وقد يؤدي التمرير إلى هذا الحد إلى الصداع.
This is also the downside I mentioned previously,
هذا هو أيضًا الجانب السلبي الذي ذكرته سابقًا،
about visual assessment being difficult in Pandas.
حول التقييم البصري الصعب في Pandas.
Uncollapsing these columns and rows is finicky,
يعد إلغاء طي هذه الأعمدة والصفوف أمرًا صعبًا،
and scrolling up and down and side to side in Jupyter Notebook cells isn't great.
والتمرير لأعلى ولأسفل وجانب إلى جنب في تطبيق Jupyter notebook ليس أمرًا رائعًا.
Instead, I like to use Pandas's Info function to get more information about our DataSet.
بدلاً من ذلك ، أحب استخدام دالة Info من Pandas للحصول على مزيد من المعلومات حول DataSet.
This is a form of programmatic assessment.
وهذا نوع من التقييم البرمجي.
This function is extremely simple.
هذه الدالة بسيطة للغاية.
We type the name of our DataFrame,
نحن نكتب اسم DataFrame،
which is df, then .Info.
الذي هو df، ثم .Info.
And again, I'll use SHIFT and TAB here,
ومرة أخرى أستخدم SHIFT وTAB هنا،
to explore the Signature and Docstring of the function.
لاستكشاف التوقيع وDocstring للدالة.
Okay. Signature, DF dot info and Docstring.
حسنًا. التوقيع، DF dot info وDocstring.
Concise summary of a DataFrame.
ملخص موجز عن DataFrame.
Docstring tells us what the function does.
يخبرنا Docstring بما تفعله الدالة.
Okay. So we'll process this cell, SHIFT and ENTER.
حسنًا. حسنًا، سنقوم بمعالجة هذه الخلية، SHIFT وENTER.
And here's that Concise Summary.
وهنا هذا الملخص الموجز.
We've got 19,001 entries and 24 columns.
لقد حصلنا على 19,001 إدخالًا و24 عمودًا.
Then, a bunch of information about each of those columns below,
ثم، مجموعة من المعلومات حول كل من هذه الأعمدة أدناه،
including the types of values in those columns
بما في ذلك أنواع القيم في تلك الأعمدة،
and the total memory usage of the DataFrame.
وإجمالي استخدام الذاكرة من DataFrame.
Okay. So let's look through these columns a bit.
حسنًا. لذلك دعونا ننظر في هذه الأعمدة قليلا.
What is ApplicationP?
ما المقصود بـ ApplicationP؟
What's AboutC?
ما المقصود بـ AboutC؟
One of the fundamentals of quality data is having descriptive variable and value names.
يتمثل أحد أساسيات بيانات الجودة في وجود متغيرات وصفية وأسماء قيمية.
Even RequiredQual, which means required qualifications, isn't that descriptive.
حتى RequiredQual، وهو ما يعني المؤهلات المطلوبة، ليس هذا الوصف.
Even JobRequirment, which has a small typo in it,
حتى JobRequirment، الذي يحتوي على خطأ مطبعي صغير،
that's descriptive enough, but you might as well fix it if we can.
وهو وصفي بقدر كافٍ، ولكن قد تقوم بإصلاحه أيضًا إذا أمكننا ذلك.
Let's make a note to clarify all of these when cleaning.
دعونا نسجل ملاحظة لتوضيح كل هذه الأمور عند التنظيف.